

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary_

Building software for the web — experienced in the Javascript and Python ecosystem.

Skills_

Languages Typescript, Javascript, Python, Perl5, C++

Tooling Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn

Frameworks React, Hapi, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Kalidokit

Industry Knowledge CI/CD, Agile Software Development, Data Structures and Algorithms

Work Experience _____

555 Comic Co.Software Development Consultant

Remote

Oct. 2022 - Dec. 2022

• Converted non-React code to React as a way to reduce possibility of bugs, and make it easy to add new features (React and Non-React code

don't mix well).
Participated in the development of a motion tracking application that converts the motion data into anime style comic through AI (essentially: real-life -> 3D model -> anime style drawing).)

Vox Sea Sdn. Bhd. Remote

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT CONSULTANT

May. 2022 - Jun. 2022

Feb. 2021 - Mar. 2021

· Created a Python utility library for formatting markdown text to its equivalent on several social media channels.

Vox Sea Sdn. Bhd.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Kuala Lumpur, Federal Territory of Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

• Use Django, Kubernetes, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build and deploy web applications.

• Guided junior developers through technical problems.

- Responsible for development of parts of a REST API that interacts with an AI back-end.
- Responsible for deployment of the back-end REST API using Kubernetes and Docker.
- Participated in daily scrum/agile meetings (technical) and weekly company meetings.
- Collaborated with other developers in building, and maintaining web applications.

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

Cyberjaya, Selangor, Malaysia

Dec. 2018 - Dec. 2020

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Learned and adopted new technology quickly (Javascript/Perl5).
- Use React, Grunt, Mobx, Webpack and SASS to build and maintain frontend applications.
- Implement a chat application by integrating SendBird's chat API.
- · Coordinate with UI/UX to implement designs for our web applications using tools such as Abstract, Zeplin and Invision.
- Collaborated with compliance to make sure our software complies with the laws.
- Use NodeJS, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build server side services for automating payments.
- · Participated in typical software development process such as sprint meetings, and code reviews.
- Autonomously outline work and set backlog along with prioritization.
- Help our recruitment team with proctoring new tech candidates in our hackathon.

Education _____

University Tunku Abdul Rahman

Kampar, Perak, Malaysia

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS (HONOURS) INFORMATION SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

May. 2021 - May. 2024

- 3.0 CGPA
- $\bullet \quad \text{Obtained an A- in "Data Structure and Algorithmic Problem Solving" which is a course introducing students to data structure and algorithms.}$
- Developing an IOT debug tool to assist in research work.